Ashish Wagle

Web Developer

Hello I am Ashish Wagle, I Studied Tribbuvan University's Bex.CsIT Program with some experience gained through student-centric projects and currently waiting for the results. I was intern at Simile Infotech as a web developer using MERN. I worked on a multi-vendor ecommerce platform as an intern. I Created facial expression analysis system with my group for college final year project. I also designed, developed and hosted personal portfolio website using python Django named 'Ashishwagle.me' where more details about me can be found.



Work History

2021-05 - Web Developer Intern

Address 2 Kathmandu Bagmati

2021-08 Simle Infotech, Kathmandu, Bagmati

44621

Developed user interfaces with modern
JavaScript frameworks, HTML5 and CSS3

Phone 986 050 0185

Education

E-mail awagle4@gmail.com

2016-11 - Bsc.CsIT

www Ashishwagle.me Current Academia International College - Gwarko

Lalitpur

2014-06 - +2 Science

2016-08 Morgan International College - Basundhara,

Kathmandu

Skills

HTML

Recognition Control of the Control o

.lavaScript Web developer Intern at Simle Infotech

2019-09 Participated in the workshop on .Net

2014-09 Advance office user certificate from Penta

Institute

Motion Graphics/ Blender

Mongo DB